Hakan Gundogdu

Frontend Developer

hakangundogdu.com



in http://linkedin.com/in/hakangundogdu1



https://github.com/hakangundogdu



Izmir, Turkey (GMT+3)



+90-532-621-7091



hakan.gundogdu@gmail.com

An enthusiastic React Frontend Developer with 2+ years of web project experiences. Possesses strong problem-solving skills, analytical and methodical thinking, transferred from finance and graphic design background. Able to work at all stages of a project life cycle. Self-motivated person with the ability to work to the highest ethical standards. Proven to work both independently and within a team. Adaptive and fast-learner of new technologies and business requirements. Effective communicator with coworkers, and project/business partners.

Areas of Expertise

- React
- Typescript
- Javascrit ES6

- Redux
- NextJS
- TailwindCSS

- HTML/CSS
- Finance / Fintech
- Git

Experience

Freelance, Turkey, 01/2019 - Now

Top-Rated-Plus Freelancer, Upwork.com

- Worked with +200 clients.
- Designed and created engaging webpages with HTML, CSS, and WordPress.
- Designed Pitch Decks and other marketing documents.
- Some of my clients: Johnson & Johnson, Novartis, Glasswall, Protective, Gateone, Abilitie

HTML, CSS, WordPress, Git, Jira, Figma, Adobe Software

Trounceflow, London, UK, 04/2019 - 08/2019

Analyst, https://wp.trounceflow.com/

- Managed Front end of the App
- Analysed financial data and created reports and insights.

HTML, CSS, WordPress, Git, Jira, Figma, Adobe Software

Other Experiences

Bayyurt Group, Financial Analyst, Turkey, 2018 – 2019

Turkish Treasury, Senior Associate, Advisor to Head of Treasury, Turkey, 2008 - 2016

Education & Credentials

BA, Bogazici University, Economics, 2007, Istanbul, Turkey

GMAT: 760 (99th percentile) **TOEFL: 106**